Guide to the Frank Clyde Brown papers, 1912-1974 RL.00160
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Cylinders and Discs, 10 boxes
  - Wax Cylinders, 1921-1935
    - RL00160-WC-0050, 1922-12-28/1922-12-29 (Box 133, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0050)
      Title: The Ploughboy, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:10:668
      Title: John Reilly, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:47:802
      Title: unknown, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:07:208
      Title: Seventy-Two, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:02:752
      Title: Barbara Allen, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:21:794
      Title: Down On the Coast of Barbary, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:50:291
    - RL00160-WC-0051, 1922-12-29 (Box 133, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0051)
      Title: Pretty Polly, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:21:394
      Title: Huxter's Bold Crew, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:37:398
      Title: William Taylor, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:07:509
      Title: Paul Jones, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:00:809
      Title: Stormy Winds, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:55:279
      Title: The Sweet Trinity (Cabin Boy), performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:42:419
      Title: Charlie Thrasher (Jolly Thrasher), performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:57:202
      Title: Scarboro Sand, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:48:624
    - RL00160-WC-0052, 1922-12-29 (Box 133, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0052)
      Title: Mary, Weep No More For Me, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:58:178
      Title: unknown, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:45:235
      Title: unknown, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:09:237
      Title: unknown, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:50:245
      Title: Storm Bird, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:50:245
      Title: The Golden Glove, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:51:687
      Title: Jack and Joe, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:01:784
      Title: Sweet Birds, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:56:829
      Title: The Prentice Boy, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:41:350
      Title: Charming Nancy (John and Nancy), performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:30:407
    - RL00160-WC-0053, undated (Box 133, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0053)
      Title: unknown, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:06:860
      Title: unknown, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:40:247
      Title: Monday Morning I Got Me A Wife, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:23:051
      Title: Little Musgrove and Lady Barnard (Lord Daniel's Wife), performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:18:466
      Title: unknown, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:22:742
      Title: unknown, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:23:833
      Title: Sweet Lulur, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:12:442
      Title: unknown, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:44:184
      Title: unknown, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:38:914
      Title: unknown, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:23:816
      Title: unknown, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:37:535
      Title: unknown, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:10:391
    - RL00160-WC-0054, 1922-12-29 (Box 133, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0054)
      Title: unknown, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:31:479
      Title: Hills of Old New Hampshire, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:49:434
      Title: Captain Glenn, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:40:610
      Title: I Could Not Call Her Mother, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:47:793
      Title: The Old Privateer, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:43:550
      Title: Nora O'Neal, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:43:499
      Title: Young Beichan (Lord Bateman), performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:49:212
      Title: Lord Thomas and Fair Annet (Lord Thomas), performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:19:421
      Title: unknown, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:37:681
      Title: unknown, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:41:037
      Title: Rose of Ardee, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:46:414
      Title: Narragansett Bay, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:59:525
    - RL00160-WC-0055, 1922-12-29 (Box 133, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0055)
      Title: A Picture of Her Boy, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:21:963
      Title: Will You Love Me When I'm Old, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:08:767
      Title: A Mother's Appeal to Her Boy, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:04:482
      Title: Saucy Anna Lee, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:27:065
      Title: Fatal Wedding, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:09:271
      Title: Her Bright Smile Haunts Me Still, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:55:161
      Title: Maggie Dear I'm Called Away, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:12:625
      Title: Kitty Kline (Kitty Clyde), performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:03:610
    - RL00160-WC-0056, 1922-12-29 (Box 133, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0056)
      Title: Alphabet of the Ship, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:27:785
      Title: Went Aloft with Jackets Blue, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:22:351
      Title: Morar, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:29:211
      Title: The White Owl With a White Head, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:26:300
      Title: Poor Jack, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:28:490
      Title: I Have No Mother Now, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:26:746
      Title: If You Will Only Be My Bride, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:33:722
      Title: Nettie Moore, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:40:236
      Title: Woodman Spare That Tree, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:21:871
      Title: Magdaline, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:09:772
      Title: Only Flirting (oh Sir, I Was Only Flirting), performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:59:539
      Title: Old Fashioned Roses, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:57:721
      Title: Have a Little Banjo Beating, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:22:125
      Title: Nancy Till, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:22:687
    - RL00160-WC-0057, 1923-02-28 (Box 133, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0057)
      Title: As I Walked Out Last Christmas Morn, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:33:529
      Title: Lord Lovel, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:23:451
      Title: The Soldier's Wooing
      Yankee Soldier (The Lady Held the Horse of a Soldier), performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:46:345
      Title: Sinful Flirting (Sinful to Flirt), performer: Faucette, C.F., location: Greenville (S.C.) | South Carolina, running time: 00:00:54:911
    - RL00160-WC-0058, 1922-12-29 (Box 133, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0058)
      Title: unknown, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:29:294
      Title: unknown, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:39:257
      Title: It Rains and It Blows, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:15:537
      Title: The Irishman's Girl, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:32:325
      Title: The Sailor Boy (Poor Little Sailor Boy), performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:00:501
      Title: New River Shore, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:24:618
      Title: At the Foot of Yonder Mountain, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:40:562
      Title: The First Girl I Courted, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:35:289
      Title: A Dark Eyed Sailor, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:35:049
      Title: There Is an Herb In Your Father's Good, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:21:175
      Title: Charlie and Mary, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:30:705
      Title: Darling Little Pink, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:40:227
      Title: The Isle of St. Helena (Napoleon), performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:57:885
      Title: The Bugle Boy, performer: Tillett, C.K., location: Roanoke Island (N.C.) | Dare County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:52:115
    - RL00160-WC-0059, 1923-07-26 (Box 133, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0059)
      Title: The Forsaken Lover, performer: Simpson, Eleanor, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:19:888
      Title: Little Mary Fagan (Little Mary Fagan and Leo), performer: Simpson, Eleanor, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:59:942
      Title: Lullaby, performer: Hauser, Jessie, location: Pfafftown (N.C.) | Forsyth County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:49:195
      Title: My Grandmother Lives On Yonder Little Green, performer: Hauser, Jessie, location: Pfafftown (N.C.) | Forsyth County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:20:995
      Title: No Sir, performer: Hauser, Jessie, location: Pfafftown (N.C.) | Forsyth County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:31:148
      Title: I'm Standing In the Shoes of John, performer: Hauser, Jessie, location: Pfafftown (N.C.) | Forsyth County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:33:148
      Title: Rig a Jig and Away We Go [Game], performer: Allen, Gertrude, location: Taylorsville (N.C.) | Alexander County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:30:301
      Title: The Owl and the Raven, performer: Allen, Gertrude, location: Taylorsville (N.C.) | Alexander County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:26:595
      Title: Shortnin' Bread, performer: Allen, Gertrude, location: Taylorsville (N.C.) | Alexander County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:12:162
      Title: Charlie Brooks, performer: Allen, Gertrude, location: Taylorsville (N.C.) | Alexander County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:17:034
      Title: Somebody, performer: Allen, Gertrude, location: Taylorsville (N.C.) | Alexander County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:15:930
      Title: Sparkin' On a Sunday Night, performer: Allen, Gertrude, location: Taylorsville (N.C.) | Alexander County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:28:380
      Title: Billy Grimes, performer: Allen, Gertrude, location: Taylorsville (N.C.) | Alexander County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:24:493
      Title: Going Up Cripple Creek [Cripple Creek], performer: Allen, Gertrude, location: Taylorsville (N.C.) | Alexander County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:06:687
      Title: Old Man, performer: Allen, Gertrude, location: Taylorsville (N.C.) | Alexander County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:18:150
      Title: I've Been Wondering All My Life, performer: Allen, Gertrude, location: Taylorsville (N.C.) | Alexander County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:12:985
      Title: Nell Cropsey (The Lexington Murder), performer: Allen, Gertrude, location: Taylorsville (N.C.) | Alexander County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:36:359
    - RL00160-WC-0060, 1923-07-24 (Box 133, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0060)
      Title: unknown, performer: Hauser, Jessie, location: Pfafftown (N.C.) | Forsyth County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:28:554
      Title: unknown, performer: Hauser, Jessie, location: Pfafftown (N.C.) | Forsyth County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:24:316
      Title: Old Grimes is Dead, performer: Frisbie, Zilpah, location: Marion (N.C.) | McDowell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:37:955
      Title: Sinful to Flirt, performer: Frisbie, Zilpah, location: Marion (N.C.) | McDowell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:33:500
      Title: Pearl Bryant (Down In a Lone Valley), performer: Frisbie, Zilpah, location: Marion (N.C.) | McDowell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:42:009
      Title: White Gal - Yaller Gal - Black Gal, performer: Frisbie, Zilpah, location: Marion (N.C.) | McDowell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:28:679
      Title: Orphan Girl, performer: Walton, Beulah, location: Morrisville (N.C.) | Wake County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:33:506
      Title: Frail Wildwood Flower, performer: Walton, Beulah, location: Morrisville (N.C.) | Wake County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:21:043
      Title: The Drunkard's Lone Child, performer: Walton, Beulah, location: Morrisville (N.C.) | Wake County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:32:547
      Title: The Stepmother, performer: Walton, Beulah, location: Morrisville (N.C.) | Wake County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:56:925
      Title: Oh Mollie Dear (Springfield Mountain), performer: Walton, Beulah, location: Morrisville (N.C.) | Wake County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:44:346
      Title: Old Nappa, performer: Walton, Beulah, location: Morrisville (N.C.) | Wake County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:27:377
      Title: Susy Gal, performer: Walton, Beulah, location: Morrisville (N.C.) | Wake County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:13:635
      Title: Poor Married Man, performer: Walton, Beulah, location: Morrisville (N.C.) | Wake County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:16:886
      Title: Meet Me In the Moonlight, performer: Walton, Beulah, location: Morrisville (N.C.) | Wake County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:29:991
  - Phonodiscs, 1936-1941
    - RL00160-PD-0001_01, circa 1936 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0001_01)
    - RL00160-PD-0001_02, 1936-07-13 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0001_02)
      Title: Old Bob Ridley, performer: Martin, H.C., location: Blowing Rock (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.) | Caldwell County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:17:282
      Title: The Old Sow, performer: Martin, H.C., location: Blowing Rock (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.) | Caldwell County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:01:659
      Title: Ace and Deuce of Diamonds, performer: Martin, H.C., location: Blowing Rock (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.) | Caldwell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:44:340
    - RL00160-PD-0002_01, 1936-08 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0002_01)
      Title: There was a little family that lived in Bethany...', performer: Wilson, Leander, location: Silverstone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:37:600
      Title: unknown, performer: Wilson, Leander, location: Silverstone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:11:543
    - RL00160-PD-0002_02, 1936-08 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0002_02)
      Title: In the Valley, performer: Wilson, Leander, location: Silverstone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:03:227
      Title: unknown, performer: Wilson, Leander, location: Silverstone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:56:010
    - RL00160-PD-0003_01, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0003_01)
      Title: Lillie Shaw, performer: Kuykendall, Otis, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:15:175
      Title: Ore Knob, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:22:537
    - RL00160-PD-0003_02, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0003_02)
      Title: Lexington Murder [variant], performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:02:28:140
    - RL00160-PD-0004_01, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0004_01)
      Title: Way out west in my sunshiny home' "Rustic Life', performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:46:323
      Title: Wagoner's Lad, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:46:352
    - RL00160-PD-0004_02, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0004_02)
      Title: Claude Allen, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:02:48:386
    - RL00160-PD-0005_01, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0005_01)
      Title: unknown, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:05:143
      Title: House Carpenter, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:18:766
    - RL00160-PD-0005_02, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0005_02)
      Title: unknown, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:03:06:663
    - RL00160-PD-0006_01, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0006_01)
      Title: unknown, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:15:292
      Title: unknown, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:53:274
      Title: George Collins, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:35:821
    - RL00160-PD-0006_02, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0006_02)
      Title: Battleship Maine (II), performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:02:11:992
      Title: Heathen Chinese, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:57:280
    - RL00160-PD-0007_01, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0007_01)
      Title: I'm Going Down the Mobile Line', performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:08:056
      Title: Banjo Music, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:03:469
      Title: Banjo Music, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:41:623
    - RL00160-PD-0007_02, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0007_02)
      Title: That Blue-Eyed Girl, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:19:165
      Title: Surely I Can Do, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:07:458
    - RL00160-PD-0008_01, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0008_01)
      Title: Banjo Music, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:56:519
      Title: Banjo Music, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:08:120
    - RL00160-PD-0008_02, 1936-07-18 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0008_02)
      Title: Banjo Music, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:01:961
      Title: My Sister On a Doola, performer: unknown, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:30:301
      Title: Wheel in a Wheel, performer: unknown, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:31:916
    - RL00160-PD-0009_01, 1936-07-18 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0009_01)
      Title: Brother are You Ready, performer: Guest, Lee | Willis, Matthew | Wilson, Booker T. | Wilson, Eugene, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:02:407
      Title: John Was A-Riding, performer: Guest, Lee | Willis, Matthew | Wilson, Booker T. | Wilson, Eugene, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:07:661
    - RL00160-PD-0009_02, 1936-07-18 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0009_02)
      Title: Stewball, performer: Guest, Lee | Willis, Matthew | Wilson, Booker T. | Wilson, Eugene, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:51:321
      Title: Just Look at the People, performer: Guest, Lee | Willis, Matthew | Wilson, Booker T. | Wilson, Eugene, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:20:386
    - RL00160-PD-0010_01, 1936-07-18 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0010_01)
      Title: Jesus Christ (I want to go to heaven), performer: Crosby, Louis | White, James | Winstead, Newman | Wolven, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:35:635
      Title: Truly, Truly, performer: Crosby, Louis | White, James | Winstead, Newman | Wolven, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:08:981
    - RL00160-PD-0010_02, 1936-07-18 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0010_02)
      Title: Where the Lord Went to Pray, performer: Crosby, Louis | White, James | Winstead, Newman | Wolven, James, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:56:127